Guide to the Brooklyn periodical illustrations BCMS.0003
Brooklyn Collection
- Beecher, Henry Ward
  - New York – The Rev. Henry Ward Beecher Stricken Down by Apoplexy, at his Home in Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, March 12, 1887 (Box 2)
  - Obituary – Henry Ward Beecher [no ill.], circa 1887 (Box 2)
  - The Old Attempt. Puck, 1885 (Box 2)
  - Out of the Fold. Puck, February 26, 1879 (Box 2)
  - Pears' Soap Advertisement Featuring Image of Beecher. Harper's Weekly, October 6, 1883 (Box 2)
  - "The Pistol Scene." Interview between Rev. Henry Ward Beecher and Mr. Francis D. Moulton. The Day's Doings, August 22, 1874 (Box 2)
  - Plymouth Church, Brooklyn NY [2 copies]. Detroit Photographic Company (Box 2)
  - The Plymouth Church Inquiry – Scene In the Parlour of Mr. Rossiter Raymond, 123 Henry Street, Brooklyn [reporters and stenographers]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, August 29, 1874 (Box 2)
  - The Plymouth Church Silver Wedding. Harper's Weekly, October 19, 1872 (Box 2)
  - Plymouth's Dying Pastor – A Faithful Wife's Untiring Vigil. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, March 19, 1887 (Box 2)
  - Plymouth Pastor-Scene at the Depot at Peekskill, N.Y. and Friday Evening Prayer Meeting in Plymouth-Church Lecture-Room. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, August 22, 1874 (Box 2)
  - Plymouth Pulpit – Rev. Henry Ward Beecher Preaching in Plymouth Church, Brooklyn. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, August 15, 1874 (Box 2)
  - The Proctor-Moulton Suit – Miss Edna Dean Proctor with her Brother and her Counsel in the United States Court on the Day of the Settlement, December 9th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, December 26, 1874 (Box 2)
  - The Remains of Henry Ward Beecher Lying in State in Plymouth Church, circa 1887 (Box 2)
  - Return of the Thirteenth Regiment, N.G.S.N.Y., from the Celebration of the Queen's Birthday in Montreal – Chaplain Henry Ward Beecher's First Appearance in Uniform in New York. Harper's Weekly, June 14, 1879 (Box 2)
  - Rev. Henry Ward Beecher. Drawing by Mr. Barry, from a photograph by Masury & Silsbee of Boston (Box 2)
  - The Reverend Henry Ward Beecher. Engraved by D.J. Pound from a photograph by Whipple & Black, Boston (Box 2)
  - Rev. Henry Ward Beecher [engraving after a photograph by Matthew Brady]. Harper's Weekly, July 17, 1858 (Box 2)
  - The Rev. Henry Ward Beecher, Pastor of Plymouth Church, Taking the Installation Oath as Chaplain of the Thirteenth Regiment, N.G.S.N.Y., At The Regimental Armory, Fulton and Flatbush Avenues, Brooklyn, March 1st. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, March 16, 1878 (Box 2)
  - Rev. Henry Ward Beecher Reading his Statement to the Plymouth Church Committee of Investigation; The Plymouth Church Investigation – Reporters of the Daily Press Following a Mysterious Witness. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, August 29, 1874 (Box 2)
  - Sensation in Plymouth Church, Caused by a Suggestive Hip-Pocket Movement of a Fanatic, April 16, 1881 [?]. (Box 2)
  - The Siege of Plymouth, 1874 (Box 2)
  - Sketches and Memorials of Henry Ward Beecher. Harper's Weekly, March 19, 1887 (Box 2)
  - The Tiltons in the Country: Mr. and Mrs. Theodore Tilton, near their Summer Boarding House on the Short-Cut Railroad, near Newburg, N.Y., in August 1870. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, September 5, 1874 (Box 2)
  - The Tilton-Beecher Trial – Portraits and Incidents. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, April 3, 1875 (Box 2)
  - The Tilton-Beecher Trial – Portraits of New Witnesses – From Sketches Made in the Courtroom. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, March 27, 1875 (Box 2)
  - The Tilton-Beecher Scandal Case [cover]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, January 30, 1875 (Box 2)
  - The Tilton-Beecher Scandal Case. – Scenes and Incidents of the Trial. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, January 30, 1875 (Box 2)
  - True Inwardness of Utah. Puck (Box 2)
  - Two Effects from Similar Causes [caption: Puck – (to Henry Ward Beecher): You see, what brought you disgrace brings him honor.]. Puck, September 10, 1879 (Box 2)
  - "Vindication!" (Box 2)
  - New York - Reception of Henry Ward Beecher at the Brooklyn Academy of Music, June 25th, on the occasion of his 70th birthday, circa 1883 (Box 2)
- Bridges: Brooklyn Bridge
  - At the Brooklyn End of the Bridge. Harper's Weekly, 1898 February 26 (Box 7)
  - Auf der East-River Brucke—Fussganger werden seekrank [On the East River bridge - pedestrians become seasick]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, undated. (Box 7)
  - Boring for a Foundation for the New Suspension Bridge from Brooklyn to New York. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1867-09-07 (Box 7)
  - Boring for Foundations for the New York and Brooklyn Suspension Bridge. Harper's Weekly, August 31, 1867. (Box 7)
  - The Break on the Brooklyn Bridge [2 copies]. Harper's Weekly, 1901 (Box 7)
  - The Bridge as Seen from the Brooklyn Side, Including the Fulton Ferry-House. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 7)
  - The Brooklyn Bridge – Cross Section of Caisson; The Brooklyn Bridge—Exterior View of Caisson. Harper's Weekly, 1870-03-19 (Box 7)
  - The Brooklyn Bridge - Dr. Scott's Ad Harper's Weekly, 1883 (Box 7)
  - Brooklyn Bridge From the North, Showing by Arrows at Center, Location of the Nine Broken Suspenders. Scientific American, 1901-08-03 (Box 7)
  - "The Brooklyn Bridge." Lithograph by S.M. Gallais, 1964 (Box 7)
  - The Brooklyn Bridge, New York – One of the wonders of the world is here, 1890 (Box 7)
  - Brooklyn-bron. Planen till denna mellan städerna New York och Brooklyn öfver East River...[Brooklyn Bridge. The plan for this tense suspension bridge between the cities of New York and Brooklyn across the East River...] [see item for full translation from Frisian], Undated. (Box 7)
  - The "Brooklyn Eagle" Office and Bridge Tower. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 7)
  - The Career of a Brave Man [color cartoons of adventurer afraid of Brooklyn Bridge cars during rush hour]. Puck, 1889 (Box 7)
  - The Cars as They Will Be on the Brooklyn Bridge [2 copies]. Harper's Weekly, 1883-06-13 (Box 7)
  - Casting the 24-ton Anchor for the Great Brooklyn Bridge at the South Brooklyn Steam Engine Works. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1873-05-24 (Box 7)
  - Connecting New York and Brooklyn by the Electric Trolley. Finishing the Great Work at the New York Terminus of the Brooklyn Bridge. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1898-01-27 (Box 7)
  - Construction of the New East River Bridge Scientific American, 1899-01-07 (Box 7)
  - Das Ver. Staaten Kriegschiff "Swatara" [The U.S. warship "Swatara." Illustration of the bridge towers with ships in the river]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1875 (Box 7)
  - Die Bogen der East-River Brucke auf der New Yorker Seite [The Arches of the East River Bridge on the New York Side]. Um Die Welt, Keppler & Schwartzmann's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1882-09-09 (Box 7)
  - Die Grosse Brooklyn Brucke [The Big Brooklyn Bridge. Cartoon of contracts changing hands between the Fowler and Kingsley Piers]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, 1872-07-05 (Box 7)
  - The East River Bridge [The Brooklyn Pier—General View of Foundation; Working Beneath Shoe or Edge of Caisson; Air Chambers for the Ingress and Egress of Workmen; Sending up Debris Through the Water Shaft; Sectional View of Foundation, Showing Caisson and Mason-Work]. Harper's Weekly, 1870-12-17 (Box 7)
  - The East River Bridge—Demolition of Buildings for the New York Approach. Harper's Weekly, 1877-11-24 (Box 7)
  - The East River Bridge, New York: Details of Air Locks for Brooklyn Caisson. Engineering, 1873-06-13 (Box 7)
  - East River Brucke.—Ansichte der Aufgange in New-York und Brooklyn [East River Bridge.—Views of the Staircases in New York and Brooklyn]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, undated. (Box 7)
  - Echoes of the late Presidential election—Paying a grotesque wager on the result—scene on Brooklyn Bridge, November 14. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1888-11-24 (Box 7)
  - Eröffnungs-Feier der New York-Brooklyner Hängebrücke am 24.Mai 1883.—Scene in der Brooklyner Brücken-Halle und das Feuerwerf auf der Brücke [Opening ceremony of the New York-Brooklyn Suspension Bridge on May 24, 1883. Scene in the Brooklyn Bridge Hall and the fireworks on the bridge]. Um Die Welt, Keppler & Schwartzmann's Illustrierte Zeitung, June 2, 1883. (Box 7)
  - The Evening Crush at a Stairway Leading to the Brooklyn Bridge. Once A Week, 1890-01-28 (Box 7)
  - An Excursion Steamer. Drawn by Charles Kendrick. Harper's Weekly, 1877-09-15 (Box 7)
  - Farrington Crossing the Span. Harper's New Monthly, 1883 (Box 7)
  - The First Passenger Across the East River Bridge.—Testing the Temporary Cable, 1876-08-25 (Box 7)
  - A Flirt's Daring Trick. National Police Gazette, 1883-05-12 (Box 7)
  - The Great Bridge – Fire-works and Illumination, from the Brooklyn Side. Drawn by Charles Graham. Harper's Weekly, 1883-06-02 (Box 7)
  - The Great East River Suspension Bridge. Connecting the Cities of New York and Brooklyn. Reprinted from color lithograph by Currier & Ives. From a 1968 calendar published by the Travelers Insurance Companies, Hartford, CT (Box 7)
  - The Great Suspension Bridge Between New York and Brooklyn. Scientific American, 1878-11-09 (Box 7)
  - The Grip on the Brooklyn Bridge—a Moment of Danger. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1890-03-08 (Box 7)
  - Inside views of the East River Bridge Caisson, Brooklyn NY. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1870-10-15 (Box 7)
  - The Jam at the Entrance to the Brooklyn Bridge. Drawing by T. de Thulstrup. Harper's Weekly, 1885-08-29 (Box 7)
  - Method of Constructing the Floor of the East River Bridge Harper's Weekly, 1881-04-23 (Box 7)
  - Most densely-traveled spot of the face of the globe. Manhattan End of Brooklyn Bridge, on the acre's area, 150,000,000 passengers gather yearly. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1903-08-20 (Box 7)
  - New Cable Driving Plant of the New York and Brooklyn Bridge. Scientific American, 1888-07-21 (Box 7)
  - New East River After the Fire. Scientific American, 1902 (Box 7)
  - The New Suspension Bridge between New York and Brooklyn USA. The Graphic, 1883-06-02 (Box 7)
  - The New Terminal in Brooklyn of the New York and Brooklyn Bridge [2 copies; 1 color]. Harper's Weekly, 1895 (Box 7)
  - New York and the Brooklyn Bridge – "On se fait a tout avec le temps,(One gets accustomed to everything in time,") is a true proverb. No doubt the old Egyptians hardly glanced at their gigantic Pyramids…", 1900 (Box 7)
  - The New York and Brooklyn Suspension-Bridge - Brooklyn Entrance Harper's Weekly [2 copies], 1883-05-26 (Box 7)
  - New York and Brooklyn Suspension Bridge., 1880 (Box 7)
  - The New York End of the Brooklyn Bridge on a Winter Day. Harper's Weekly, 1892-02-20 (Box 7)
  - New York Harbor, as Seen from the Brooklyn Tower of the Suspension Bridge. Harper's Weekly, 1873 November 1 (Box 7)
  - The New York Terminal of the Brooklyn Bridge, Now under Construction. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 7)
  - New York's Workers as They Are, and Not as Jeff Davis Saw Them. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1909 (Box 7)
  - Old and New - the Two Bridges Connecting New York and Brooklyn. Harper's Weekley, 1901 (Box 7)
  - Our Artist in America: New York City People Going Home. The Illustrated London News, undated. (Box 7)
  - The Present Condition of the Anchorage of the East River Bridge. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1873-08-30 (Box 7)
  - Present Condition of the New East River Bridge Scientific American, 1902-07-26 (Box 7)
  - A Promenade in Mid-Air: Crossing the Footway of the New York and Brooklyn Suspension Bridge. The Pictorial World (Box 7)
  - Promenade, Railway, and Roadway of the Brooklyn Bridge. Scientific American, 1883-06-02 (Box 7)
  - The Proposed Extension of the East River Bridge. Harper's Weekly, 1886 (Box 7)
  - The Proposed Terminal of the East River Bridge in Brooklyn. Harper's Weekly, 1893-03-11 (Box 7)
  - R.G. Odlum springt am 19 Mai 1885 von der East River Brucke in den Fluss [R.G. Odlum jumps from the East River Bridge into the river, May 19 1885]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung (Box 7)
  - Rapid Transit in New York – The Crush at the Brooklyn Bridge. Drawn by Arthur Lewis. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Weekly, 1904-09-15 (Box 7)
  - A Runaway on the Brooklyn Side of the East River Bridge [2 copies; 1 color], Undated (Box 7)
  - Section of Bridge, Showing Foot, Rail and Carriage Ways; Bridge Approaches. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 7)
  - Shoveling Snow from the East River Bridge, New York City. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1885-01-10 (Box 7)
  - Sinking the Brooklyn Caisson for East River Bridge No. 3 Scientific American, 1902-05-31 (Box 7)
  - The Tragedy on the Brooklyn Bridge, May 30. Drawn by C.Graham and W.A. Rogers. Harper's Weekly, 1883-06-09 (Box 7)
  - "Under the Towers" from the water-color painting by F. Hopkinson Smith. Harper's Weekly, 1882-02-18 (Box 7)
  - Unglück auf der East-River Bruecke. Der Bruch eines Drahtseiles verursacht den Tod zweier Arbeiter [Misfortune on the East River Bridge. The breakage of a wire rope causes the death of two workers]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, undated. (Box 7)
  - View of Caisson and Plant for New East River Bridge Scientific American, 1897-08-07 (Box 7)
  - View showing the proposed improvement at the New York terminus of the Brooklyn Bridge. Scientific American, 1884-04-12 (Box 7)
  - Washington A. Roebling, the Invalid Engineer in Chief of the Brooklyn Bridge, Watching the Progress of the Structure from his Sick Room on Brooklyn Heights. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1884-05-26 (Box 7)
  - Welcoming Admiral Dewey—Pyrotechnic Display in the Harbor and Rivers, Illumination of the Brooklyn Bridge at Night. Drawn from Life by G.W. Peters. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 7)
- Bridges: Other
  - The Aeronautics of Bridge-Building: Constructing the New Manhattan Bridge. Harper's Weekly, 1909 [?] (Box 2)
  - The Brooklyn Bridge and Suspension Bridge No. 3, on Which Work Has Just Commenced. Scientific American, 1901-08-03 (Box 2)
  - The East River Bridge, New York: Showing the Present Progress of the Work. Harper's Weekly, 1901-07-27 (Box 2)
  - The Greatest Suspension Bridge in the World. Laying the First Cables of the New East River Bridge Connecting New York and Brooklyn, Undated. (Box 2)
  - The Last Cable Laid. Views of the New Brooklyn Bridge Taken on the Occasion of the Completion of the First Great Stage of the Work when on June 26 the Last Strand of the Last Cable was Strung across the River [Manhattan Bridge]. Harper's Weekly, 1902 (Box 2)
  - The New Bridge over the East River, New York [Drawn by H. Louis Sonntag, Jun.]. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 2)
  - New East River Bridge Connecting New York and Brooklyn. Scientific American, 1896-09-12 (Box 2)
  - The New Ship-Canal at Kingsbridge, Connecting the Harlem and Hudson Rivers. Harper's Weekly, undated. (Box 2)
  - New York's Newest Bridge. The Perilous Footway on the Temporary Cables of the Manhattan Bridge, Undated. (Box 2)
  - Perilous Work of Steel-bridge Builders [likely a drawing of workers on the Manhattan Bridge; construction began 1901 and was completed 1909]. Leslie's Weekly, 1905-06-08 (Box 2)
  - Proposed Bridge Over the Hudson River, at New York [proposed bridge to be built at 69th street in Manhattan crossing the Hudson]. Scientific American, 1894-06-16 (Box 2)
  - Spanning the East River with the World's Greatest Steel Suspension Bridge, Completion of the Four Temporary Foot-Bridges Which Are to Be Used in Assembling the Enormous Cables. Leslie's Weekly, undated. (Box 2)
  - View of East River Bridge from Brooklyn, Showing Temporary Footway Cables. Scientific American, 1903 (Box 2)
  - Williamsburg and the Brooklyn Bridges., 1904 (Box 2)
- Brighton Beach
  - Brighton Beach Bathing Pavilion, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Brighton Pier and Navigation Co., West Brighton, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Depot of Prospect Park and Coney Island R.R, West Brighton, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Feltman's Ocean Pavilion, West Brighton Beach, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Hotel Brighton, Brighton Beach, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Incidents of the Excursion of the American Medical Association to Brighton Beach, June 4th, 1880 (Box 2)
  - Mrs. Vanderveer's Bathing Pavilion, West Brighton Beach, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Observatory at West Brighton, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Ocean Pier and Navigation Co., West Brighton, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Paul Bauer's West Brighton Hotel. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - Sea Beach Palace Hotel, West Brighton, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - The Sea-Side Home for Children, West Brighton Beach, Coney Island. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 2)
  - The Silhouette Artist and the City Belle –An Evening Scene on Brighton Beach. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1879-07-19 (Box 2)
  - Summer Night's Festival of the Arion Singing Society at West Brighton Beach, July 31st – Meeting of Arion and Neptune on the Beach after Landing from the Dolphins. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1879-08-16 (Box 2)
  - New York's Great Midsummer Attraction. Life, 1902-07-24 (Box 2)
- Brooklyn Academy of Music
  - Academy of Music and Academy of Design, undated (Box 7)
  - Brooklyn Academy of Music. From a 1959 Dime Savings Bank of Brooklyn Calendar [image is older than calendar] (Box 7)
  - The Brooklyn Academy of Music – Exterior; The Brooklyn Academy of Music – Interior – Opening Concert, January 15, 1861. Harper's Weekly, 1861-02-02 (Box 7)
  - Grand Ball, for the benefit of the Home for Destitute Children, at the Academy of Music, Brooklyn, February 5th. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1880-02-21 (Box 7)
  - Reception of the Brooklyn Art Association at the Brooklyn Academy of Music [color]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1863-03-28 (Box 7)
  - Reception of the Brooklyn Art Association at the Brooklyn Academy of Music [German language; black & white]. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1863-04-04 (Box 7)
  - Roof of Academy of Music Blown Off by Gale. Harper's Weekly, 1860-07-14 (Box 7)
- Brooklyn Art Association
  - New Academy of the Brooklyn Art Association. Harper's Weekly, 1872 March 23 (Box 2)
- Brooklyn Heights
  - Brooklyn Heights, Opposite the City of New York [color]. Gleason's Pictorial, 1854 November 25 (Box 2)
  - Brooklyn Heights Water-Cure Establishment. Life Illustrated, 1859 [?] (Box 2)
- Celebrations
  - The Brooklyn Columbian Celebration – High-School boys marching up Court Street – Grand Army Procession from top of Memorial Arch – City Hall Decorations – Court House Decorations – Memorial Arch – Daughters of the Grand Army of the Republic – Ranks of red, white and blue, undated (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn Honors Her Brave Soldiers and Sailors: A Magnificent Ovation by Her Citizens to the Men Who Served in the War with Spain – The Review at Prospect Park Plaza on Saturday, October 1st. [2 copies]. Leslie's Weekly, October 20, 1898 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn Sunday School Celebration. Harper's Bazaar, June 20, 1874 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn's Enthusiastic Reception of Her Great Arctic Explorer [Frederick Cook's Return]. Leslie's Weekly, September 20, 1909 (Box 3)
  - Brooklyn's Welcome to Governor Cleveland – The Procession Passing the City Hall [2 copies]. Drawn by Schell and Hogan. Harper's Weekly, October 25, 1884 (Box 3)
  - A Children's Festival Day: The Thirty-Second Annual Parade of the Sunday Schools of Brooklyn. Photographs by Hemment. Frank Leslie's Weekly, June 22, 1893 (Box 3)
  - Colored Celebration of Emancipation Day at Myrtle Avenue Park. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, August 9, 1884 (Box 3)
  - The Columbian Celebration in New York City. Illumination and firework at Brooklyn Bridge. Frank Leslie's Weekly, October 20, 1892 (Box 3)
  - Das 14 National-Sangerfest [Fourth of July Celebration]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, July 18, 1885 (Box 3)
  - A Democratic Barbecue. – The Hungry Crowd of "Unterrified" Clamoring or Cuts of the Toothsome Roast. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, October 18, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Fire-Works at New York on the Evening of the Fourth of July, As Seen From Brooklyn Heights. Harper's Weekly, 1859 (Box 3)
  - Grand Gathering of Sunday School Children at Prospect Park, in Celebration of the Anniversary, May 28th, 1873. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, June 14, 1873 (Box 3)
  - The Inauguration of Governor David B. Hill, at Albany January 1st—the Procession Passing the Reviewing Stand. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, January 12, 1889 (Box 3)
  - Monster Picnic at Schach's Park, East Brooklyn, June 13, for the Benefit of the German Hospital Fund – From a Sketch by Our Special Artist, 1864 (Box 3)
  - The Naval Ball in Honor of the Grand Duke Alexis, at the Brooklyn Navy-Yard. Harper's Weekly, December 16, 1871 (Box 3)
  - New York – Fifteenth Annual Reunion, in Brooklyn, June 11th, of the Society of the Army of the Potomac – The Procession Passing Under the Grand Arch in Montague Street, 1884 (Box 3)
  - The Republican Barbecue in Brooklyn: Roasting the oxen; Procession of the Boys in Blue [2 copies, b&w and color]. Harper's Weekly, November 11, 1876 (Box 3)
  - Überreichung von medaillen durch manor booth von Brooklyn an die Veteren der Brooklyner Regimenter in Front Green, am 25 Oktober 1866 [Presentation of Medals]. Frank Leslie's Illustrierte Zeitung, October 25, 1866 (Box 3)
  - Welcome Army of the Potomac – drawing of parade on Montague Street [German language], circa 1884 (Box 3)
  - Parade of the Brooklyn Sunday-School Children. Harper's Bazaar, June 13, 1868 (Box 3)
- Cemeteries
  - A Day in Greenwood Cemetery. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper, 1867 August 17 (Box 3)
  - Decorating the Three Thousand Soldiers' Graves in Cypress Hill Cemetery, Near Brooklyn, Long Island. Sketched by Stanley Fox. Harper's Weekly, June 20, 1868 (Box 3)
  - Decoration of the graves of Union soldiers at Cypress Hills Cemetery, Brooklyn, New York, May 30, 1869. Sketched by Stanley Fox. Harper's Weekly, June 19, 1869 (Box 3)
  - Dedication of the Actors' Monument in the Cemetery of the Evergreens. Drawn by Graham and Rogers. Harper's Weekly, June 18, 1887 (Box 3)
  - Engine House – 1855 [Greenwood Cemetery] (Box 3)
  - Entrance to Greenwood Cemetery, 1845. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Firemen's Monument in Greenwood Cemetery. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Firemen's Monument, Situated on Ocean Hill, in Greenwood Cemetery, Long Island, N.Y. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, October 18, 1851 (Box 3)
  - Floral Decoration of the Graves of Patriot Soldiers, at Cypress Hill Cemetery, Long Island, New York, May 31st. Frank Leslie's Illustrated Newspaper (Box 3)
  - Fountain and Reservoir on Fountain Hill [Greenwood Cemetery] (Box 3)
  - Gardener's Lodge (Battle Hill), Greenwood Cemetery [2 copies]. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Gardener's Lodge, Ocean Hill – 1845 [Greenwood Cemetery] (Box 3)
  - Greenwood Cemetery: Entrance to Greenwood Cemetery; Monument in Greenwood Cemetery. Gleason's Pictorial Drawing Room Companion, circa 1851 (Box 3)
  - Greenwood Cemetery in Brooklyn (Box 3)
  - Lawn-Girt Hill Greenwood Cemetery (Box 3)
  - Monument to Miss Charlotte Canda (Green-Wood Cemetery). Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Northern Entrance to Greenwood (From Within) [2 copies]. Stiles, History of Kings County, 1884 (Box 3)
  - Outer Gate, Northern Entrance [Greenwood Cemetery] (Box 3)